# **RUDOLPH PEREIRA**

# Frontend Developer

노 +971 509712683 / +91 9819468208 @ rudolph.pereira93@gmail.com & http://rudolphpereira.com 🗣 UAE

SUMMARY

A self-starting Front-end Developer with experience in building responsive websites. Proficient in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and modern libraries that are geared toward optimum user experiences.

An individual with strong communication skills and problem solving abilities with a background in market research analysis.

Kindly view my projects through the link mentioned above.

EXPERIENCE

# UI/UX Developer - Frontend

Planet Green Solutions 2022 - Present UAE - Onsite

- Built the entire front end single-handedly for websites in the government and private sector, utilizing the bundle built by the design house. Tech stack includes React, JavaScript, jQuery, SASS, CSS
- Built the entire front end for a web app for the Federal Tax Authority -**UAE.** Built reusable components and maintained a streamlined design pattern across the web app
- Government sector website projects built include The Education and **Human Resource Council, The Roads General Authority for Saudi Arabia and more**
- Private sector projects built include Glaze The Strongest brand in the natural stone industry
- Built new updates for over 20 existing client websites and also conducted bug fixes to enhance user experience
- Maintained updates on the company website

#### UI/UX Developer - Frontend

SCNext 2021 - 2022 UAE - Onsite

- Built the entire User Interface for the Peridot web app single-handedly using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap and JavaScript - over 50 pages
- Built reusable components that were utilized across 50 product pages
- Maintained updates on company website using Elementor WordPress

## UI/UX Developer - Frontend

Keywordio 2020 - 2021 India - Remote

- · Building pixel perfect responsive landing pages using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap and JavaScript - React
- Debugging and refactoring existing code
- Building reusable components on HubSpot and WordPress

STRENGTHS

Highly Proactive & Analytical

SKILLS

#### Languages

**JavaScript** HTML5 CSS3

## **Tools and Libraries**



CERTIFICATIONS

#### **Human-Computer Interaction**

The Interaction Design Foundation

EDUCATION

## Bachelor of Mass Media

University of Mumbai 2011 - 2014

Major in Advertising & Marketing